

GIANNE RAYANDAYAN GRAPHIC DESIGNER/ILLUSTRATOR/UX DESIGNER

PORTFOLIO: GRAYANDAY.COM GRAYANDA17@GMAIL.COM (858) 386-4554



EDUCATION

ABOUT ME



University of California, San Dlego

I am a motivated, detail-oriented, and adaptable individual with a passion B.S. Cognitive Science w/ Specialization for communication and provocation through design. I effectively collaborate in Human Computer Interaction with designers, engineers, and clients to produce quality work in a timely manner. 2013-2017



SKILLS

Adobe llustrator

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe InDesign

Adobe Premiere Pro

Unbounce

Processing

MATLAB

HTML/CSS/Javascript



METHODS

Visual Design

Wireframing

Rapid Prototyping

User Research

Competitive Analysis

User Personas

User Flows

Affinity Diagrams

Parallel Design

EXPERIENCE



Tutor/Lead Tutor UCSD Computer Science Department

March 2015-June 2017

- Tutored students of varying skill-levels and backgrounds on basic coding principles through HTML, CSS, Excel, and MATLAB
- Worked with a team of tutors, delegated tasks, and managed multiple weekly labs
- Developed labs and homework and presented revised drafts to tutor team during weekly meetings for critique and feedback.
- Mediated class online forum by answering student questions and emails

Graphic Design Intern UCSD Revelle College

September, 2016-June 2017

- Collaborated with photographers and designers to create advertisements, logos, and print items for student events.
- Corresponded with UCSD Revelle College Administrative Staff and student leaders to facilitate projects from beginning to completion

Designer / Video Editor Racebending.com

July 2017

- Compiled and edited footage of Racebending's Super Asian America Comic Con 2017 panel footage for viewing on racebending.com and youtube.com
- Designed in-video graphical content to highlight panel's keynote speakers on Asian-American representation in media

UX Researcher UCSD Mental Wellness Needfinding Project

March 2016 - June 2016

- Directed team's needfinding research on various student groups to understand the complexity of mental health stigma among UCSD students.
- Derived conclusions from surveys, interviews, and observation by creating affinity diagrams and language analysis
- · Assisted with writing team's Design Brief and presenting team's work

Graphic/UX Designer Design Startup Project "Wonder Plates"

March 2017 - June 2017

- Conducted qualitative surveys and user testing to promote data driven design of a cultural meal prep service.
- Collaborated with team members to develop startup's branding and promotional materials
- · Directed and edited startup's promotional video

Graphic Designer Political Design Project

Jan. 2017 - March 2017

- Worked with a team to create a provocative redesign of UCSD's Sun God Music Festival advertisement campaign to bring attention to issues of deteriorating student event quality
- Designed final advertisement posters and Facebook ad banners to increase traffic towards mock event site for petition signatures